<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fwknop2</string>
    <string name="title_config_detail">Config Detail</string>
    <string name="QR_Code">Capture qr</string>
    <string name="detail_help">Help</string>
    <string name="Save">Save config</string>
    <string name="Delete">Delete config</string>
    <string name="knock">Send knock</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_options">
        <item>Resolve IP</item>
        <item>Source IP</item>
        <item>Allow IP</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="configtype_options">
        <item>Open Port</item>
        <item>Nat Access</item>
        <item>Server Command</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ssh_options">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>SSH Uri</item>
        <item>Juicessh</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="help_page">
 <![CDATA[
 <p>
 Welcome to fwknop2! This app is for the sending of SPA Packets to a Linux host or router, mainly
 for opening ports in an iptables firewall. More info
 <a href="https://www.cipherdyne.org/fwknop/">at the Cipherdyne web site</a>.
 </p>
 <p>
 Get started by selecting "New Config" from the menu, and then filling in at least "Nickname", "Server Address",
 and "Rijndael Key." If you are using luci-app-fwknop on an Openwrt router, you can select the "Capture qr" option from the menu,
  and use a qr code generated on the router to auto fill the key and hmac data.
  </p>
<p>If Juicessh is installed, you can autostart a saved Juicessh connection by sellecting Juicessh from the
 "Run SSH App" menu, and after a brief delay, choosing the desired connection. If you want to use a different
  SSH app, select "SSH Uri", and then type in your desired Username to connect as. This will use the system\'s
  default ssh client to try to connect to the port you are opening.
 </p>
 <p>
  Once the data is filled in, select "Save Config" from the menu. Then, to send a SPA knock, long tap the
   Saved config you want to use, and select "Send Knock"
 </p>

 <p>Credits: Based on fwknop and libfko written by <a href="https://www.cipherdyne.org/fwknop/"> Michael Rash</a></p>
 <p>This app was written by <a href="http://incomsystems.biz/"> Jonathan Bennett</a></p>
 <p>This app is open source software. The source can be found  <a href="https://github.com/oneru/Fwknop2">on github</a>. Please report any bugs here.</p>
 <p> The fwknop2 icon is derived from on a photo by <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/anemoneprojectors/5330583056/">Peter O\'Connor</a></p>

 <b>Tap the back button to get started.</b>
 </p>
 ]]>
 </string>
</resources>
